sup everyone timbers only factor with a
very special video today today I'll be
doing a review of something that is very
special is of - Sonic Underground
puzzles that got off of ebay via the
official Sonic on pus mobile puzzle
figure figures they made of foam and
[ __ ] and they're very expensive I got
two Knuckles the Echidna wine and the
son of the Hedgehog one Sonia cost me
like 86 bucks
Knuckles was like like seven but 7778
box and [ __ ] so yeah I'm gonna be
reviewing them when I bought Sonia it
was like it was like dried [ __ ] on it so
I I can't think of a said what's up with
that
and he's sending that [ __ ] apologizing
and instead of having me send a place he
just sent me another one
so yeah shove it you [ __ ] York York
you're a pretty cool dude as you can see
this one I got for placement I'm gonna
keep the one covered each it - or some
and this one says oh no am I gonna keep
it that way because I heard like soccer
Moshe KKnux on opening this puzzle of
rock it cost like two thousand bucks or
some [ __ ]
so yeah that's like that's that's pretty
cool now let's get into a V level one
first of all this is the this is the
Sonja puzzle as you can see it's got a
stand
Knuckles actually has a stand - it's
like not cause like stands like that and
[ __ ] what's really cool as puzzles is
look at that there are three dimensional
it's like having not gonna be a kid not
in your house and [ __ ] they're also two
double-sided it kind of messes up with
arc
I mean it's pretty cool I don't see
anything wrong with it well I think
you're so cool that is because because
these are foam puzzles you can like take
off the basin [ __ ] and you can actually
like use them as like action figures and
um ditches and you catch you like mixing
masterpiece because there's like a bunch
of them so I'm gonna take off like Sonia
shoes and knuckle shoes and if you plug
it it almost looks like no cuz it's like
he'slooking Sonia shoes I mean not quite
but you get on me [ __ ] black if I put
on like that well yeah that's just
that's pretty much it Sonia others like
so you more like those you [ __ ]
so yeah already has already like knocked
in of ten perfect school in [ __ ] so yeah
I bye
I did it I'm I did bad so now I'm gonna
to go into detail about something a lot
of people do not seem to understand I'm
seeing everyone on the internet from
stupid [ __ ] who seem to think that
Manic the Hedgehog has a puzzle mobile
that is false the Archos whoever got
puzzles is strong even Hedgehog a
brother song I got one dr. Robotnik has
no because not on his box but dr. Bach
does have one and Knuckles the Echidna
nobody else I wish Bobby got one but not
getting what gave me two [ __ ]
although yeah Manic the Hedgehog I don't
know why if you go on a bunch of
websites good evening videos of [ __ ]
saying Amanda the Hedgehog one does
exist they are lying to you they are
trying to trick you may I try to make
you look like a dumbass [ __ ] because
some magnetic puzzle it does not exist
how do I know this well I actually visit
the studio where the sock Underground
puzzle goes were made I asked him I went
to him I said [ __ ] where is the how
come you never make the Hedgehog Cosmo
because I've been when I went through
the store we was like a [ __ ] baby and
[ __ ] I would like I was like crying and
[ __ ] saying mom daddy what you saw what
is by American Baldy and my parents they
were like big I don't know Esther does
it make yourself and then I'm like a
couple years later I did and I was I was
I was pissed I was I kid you not I I got
I got on my bicycle I rode to his house
with you in like a whole nother [ __ ]
stay there
my parents got pissed off but what are
you gonna do I it's what I gotta do for
sucking around you know what I mean
anyways I rode my bicycle into up into
that bitch's driveway I pulled out like
a baseball bat cuz I was gonna [ __ ] I
was gonna be his ass and then he luckily
he was just getting just off of work I
said [ __ ] this guess what this bill
that is going unless you tell me what is
the box where's the Manic possible and
then he told me listen timbers one of
the five there is no magic pause I was
like what and he said man exhale was
just too big they could not make it and
that's that was it Manic people seem to
think sauna so you all have a puzzle
because the triplets or some [ __ ] like
trio but no Manic never got one I have
fruit I went to him if you don't if you
don't believe you can trust my word
because a Mack the Hedgehog puzzle does
not exist so yeah these poles are pretty
cool I have so much fun playing with
them and [ __ ] like role-playing [ __ ]
it's pretty cool I mean I suggest you
buy them because it's like a little
piece of saw this is a piece a Sonic
around history that will not be in the
wall for very long if you don't buy
these somebody else will and when that
happens it's it's done what are you
gonna do then [ __ ] when these are gone
the gone that's that sock enough for you
it's like it's like a legacy in all its
own
when soccer merchandise goes out of
stock it's not coming back
oh when was the last time you saw these
puzzles in the flood stock is not known
that often is that right yeah [ __ ] I'm
special because I have these
you won't do you get that [ __ ] [ __ ]
as I saying this one these comes back
100 bucks and [ __ ]
so yeah it's that small pasta paid for
me but other people they can't justify
some ways I don't understand why they
can't just without I can